<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Appathon</string>

    <string name="pedu">The solution proposed in RFC 827
        was that the ARPANET be migrated from a single internetwork
        to a system of interconnected, autonomously controlled
        internetworks. Within each internetwork, known as an
        autonomous system (AS), the administrative authority
        for that AS is free to manage the internetwork as it
        chooses. In effect, the concept of autonomous systems
        broadens the scope of internetworking and adds a new layer
        of hierarchy. Where there was a single internetwork—a network
        of networks—there is now a network of autonomous systems,
        each of which is itself an internetwork. And just as a
        network is identified by an IP address, an AS is identified by
        an autonomous system number. An AS number is a 16-bit number
        assigned by the same addressing authority that assigns IP addresses.
</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">Main2Activity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_primaryeducation">Primaryeducation</string>
    <string name="title_activity_highereducation">Highereducation</string>

    <string name="Hedu">●     With all gateways knowing all routes, "the overhead of the routing algorithm becomes excessively
        large." Whenever a topology change occurs, the likelihood of which increases with the size of the internetwork,
        all gateways have to exchange routing information and recalculate their tables. Even when the internetwork
        is in a steady state, the size of the routing tables and routing updates becomes an increasing burden. ●
        As the number of GGP software implementations increases, and the hardware platforms on which they are
        implemented become more diverse, "it becomes impossible to regard the Internet as an integrated
        communications system." Specifically, maintenance and troubleshooting become "nearly impossible." ●
        As the number of gateways grows, so does the number of gateway administrators. As a result,
        resistance to software upgrades increases: "[A]ny proposed change must be made in too many
        different places by too many different people."
</string>
    <string name="title_activity_job">Scheme</string>

    <string name="Job1">he Ministry has been administering ‘Support to Training and Employment Programme
        for Women (STEP) Scheme’ since 1986-87 as a ‘Central Sector Scheme’. The STEP Scheme aims to provide
        skills that give employability to women and to provide competencies and skill that enable women to become
        self-employed/entrepreneurs. The Scheme is intended to benefit women who are in the age group of 16 years
        and above across the country. The grant under the Scheme is given to an institution/ organisation including
        NGOs directly and not the States/ UTs. The assistance under STEP Scheme will be available in any sector for
        imparting skills related to employability and entrepreneurship, including but not limited to the Agriculture,
        Horticulture, Food Processing, Handlooms, Tailoring, Stitching, Embroidery, Zari etc, Handicrafts, Computer
        IT enable services along with soft skills and skills for the work place such as spoken English, Gems , Jewellery, Travel ,
        Tourism, Hospitality. </string>
    <string name="Job2">The Union Ministry of Women and Child Development plans to
        appoint Mahila Police Volunteers in every village in the country to enhance
        protection to women and children.
        Disclosing this to presspersons here on Sunday, Maneka Gandhi, Union Minister
        for Women and Child Development, said that the process of appointing the
        volunteers would begin soon. They would be paid a nominal honorarium.</string>
    <string name="Job3">Every Year, Ministry of Women  Child Development celebrates International
Women Day on 8th March. The significance of the International Women’s Day lies in
our re-affirmation of improve the condition of women, especially those at the
margins of our society and empower them to take rightful place in society.
Ministry of Women and Child Development, has revised the guidelines for
Women Awards for conferring on eminent women, organisations and institutions.
These awards will be called “Nari Shakti Puruskars”. Now, from the year 2016,
20 Nari Shakti Puruskars shall be conferred every year. The awards will be
conferred on 8th March on the occasion of International Women’s Day (IWD). The
Award in each category shall carry a Certificate and a cash amount. The award
would be given to eminent or outstanding Institutions or organizations and
individuals.
With the institution of these awards all the earlier women awards given by the
Ministry of Women Child Development ceased to exist.</string>
    <string name="Job4">Recognizing the need to prevent women from exploitation and to support their
survival and rehabilitation, the scheme of Short Stay Home for women and girls was
introduced as a social defense mechanism, by the then Department of Social Welfare in 1969.
The scheme is meant to provide temporary accommodation, maintenance and rehabilitative
services to women and girls rendered homeless due to family discord, crime, violence, mental
stress, social ostracism or are being forced into prostitution and are in moral danger. Another
scheme with the similar objectives namely Swadhar –A Scheme for Women in Difficult
Circumstances was launched by the Department of Women and Child Development in 2001-
02. The scheme through the provisions of shelter, food, clothing, counseling, training, clinical
and legal aid aims to rehabilitate such women in difficult circumstance. Centre for Market
Research and Social Development, New Delhi conducted an evaluation in 2007 to assess the
performance of both the schemes. The evaluation report while citing the effectiveness and
positive impact of measures adopted under the schemes for counseling and rehabilitation
found that the profile and category of residents, admission procedure, counseling, quality of
service, vocational training, rehabilitation and follow up procedure are almost similar in both
the schemes. It, therefore, recommended merger of these two schemes for better functioning
and outcomes with lesser administrative burdens and procedures. It also recommended that
the new scheme should focus on establishing one such home in every district.
The positive findings of the evaluation study has encouraged the Ministry to propose
this new scheme that would target the women victims of unfortunate circumstances who are
in need of institutional support for rehabilitation so that they could lead their life with dignity. </string>
    <string name="Job5">The objective of the scheme is to promote availability of safe and
conveniently located accommodation for working women, with day care facility for
their children, wherever possible, in urban, semi urban, or even rural areas where
employment opportunity for women exist. To achieve this objective, the scheme will assist
projects for construction of new hostel buildings, expansion of existing hostel buildings and
hostel buildings in rented premises. The working women’s hostel projects being assisted
under this scheme shall be made available to all working women without any distinction with
respect to caste, religion, marital status etc., subject to norms prescribed under the scheme.
While the projects assisted under this scheme are meant for working women, women under
training for job may also be accommodated in such hostels subject to the condition that
taken together, such trainees should not occupy more than 30% of the total capacity the
hostel and they may be accommodated in the hostels only when adequate numbers of
working women are not available. Children of working women, up to the age of 18 years for
girls and up to the age of 5 years for boys may be accommodated in such hostel with their
mothers.</string>
    <string name="Pension1">Eligibility: Individuals aged 60 years and above living below
        the poverty line
     Amount: ₹200 (US$3.00) per month for beneficiaries aged 60–79 and ₹500 (US$7.40)
        per month for those 80 years and above.</string>
    <string name="Pension2">Any Citizen of India, aged between 18 years and 40 years, who has his/her savings bank
        account opened and also possesses a mobile number, would be eligible to subscribe to this scheme.

Government Funding – Indian Government would provide (i) fixed pension guarantee for the subscribers; (ii) would
        co-contribute 50% of the subscriber contribution or Rs. 1,000 per annum, whichever is lower, to eligible
        subscribers; and (iii) would also reimburse the promotional and development activities including
        incentive to the contribution collection agencies to encourage people to join the APY.</string>
    <string name="Pension3">A centrally sponsored scheme implemented in the State where
        the beneficiaries receive pension ® Rs. 300/- per month under the Scheme.
Target Group:
Widows within the age of 40 years and above in the BPL category. The total target at present
        is 1,94,379 (40-59 years) and 3,34,191(60-79 years) totaling to 5,28,570 beneficiaries.</string>
    <string name="Pension4"> cash incentive of Rs. 4000 to women (19 years and above) for the first two live births</string>
    <string name="Pension5">tackle malnutrition and health problems in children below 6 years of age and their mothers</string>
    <string name="title_activity_splash">Splash</string>
    <string name="title_activity_pension">Pension</string>
    <string name="title_activity_job1">Tranning and Employment Programme for Women</string>
    <string name="title_activity_job2">Mahila Police Volunteer</string>
    <string name="title_activity_job3">NARI SHAKTI PURASKAR</string>
    <string name="title_activity_job4">GOVERNMENT OF INDIA</string>
    <string name="title_activity_job5">SWADHAR Greh (A Scheme for Women in Difficult Circumstances)","Working Women Hostel</string>
    <string name="title_activity_pension1">Indira Gandhi National Old Age Pension Scheme (IGNOAPS)</string>
    <string name="title_activity_pension2">Launching Atal Pension Yojana (APY) from June 1, 2015</string>
    <string name="title_activity_pension3">Indira Gandhi National Widow Pension</string>
    <string name="title_activity_pension4">Indira Gandhi Matritva Sahyog Yojana</string>
    <string name="title_activity_pension5">Integrated Child Development Services</string>
    <string name="title_activity_get_started"> </string>

    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_category">category</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2_activity_login">Main2ActivityLogin</string>
    <string name="title_activity_data_base_helper">DataBaseHelper</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login_data_base_adapter">LoginDataBaseAdapter</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main_activity_l">MainActivityL</string>
    <string name="title_activity_sign_up">SignUPActivity</string>
</resources>
